
NET is an umbrella term which comprises of FCL (Framework Class Library) and many languages(C#, VB.NET, C++/CLI,...),  which compiles source code and outputs IL (Intermediate Language). IL will be consumed by CLR (Common Language Runtime) and converts it into platform specific code during runtime by the JIT (just-in-time) compiler.
C# is a programming language using which you can develop software utilizing the FCL and can target many platforms (Windows, Linux - using Mono, iOS - using Xamarin, ...)
C# - A programing language developed by Microsoft for .NET
.NET - Framework built by Microsoft

