1.Code::Blocks is an extensible and fully configurable IDE for C, C++ and Fortran and is designed to support its users most demanding needs
2.CodeLite-an open source, cross platform ID for C, C++, PHP, and Node.js coding languages, CodeLite works across all major platforms.
3.DialogBlocks-A cross platform GUI coding assistant, DialogBlocks is a simple tool that enables you to easily edit dialogs and generate code. 
4.NetBeans-An intuitive, drag-and-drop interface with project templates, binary and static libraries, and many useful functions to make your life simpler, NetBeans is a popular IDE for C and C++ projects
5.Komodo-Komodo is a comprehensive IDE that supports all major programming languages, providing a single tool that meets your development needs across the spectrum. 
6.Aptana Studo 3-Aptana, recently acquired by Appcelerator, offers one of the most powerful open-source IDEs: Aptana Studo 3
7.Squad-A web-based IDE, Squad simplifies collaboration with the ability to open, edit, and share files in real time, from any web browser. 
8.Cloud 9 IDE-A powerful, flexible IDE, Cloud 9 allows you to collaborate publicly or privately in workspaces.
9.Xcode IDE-Xcode IDE is a component of Xcode 5, a complete set of tools for building and deploying apps in the Apple environment.
10.Coda 2-Coda 2 is a refreshed version of the original, with the same Editor, Terminal, CSS, Files, and other essentials for building functional web applications, enhanced with a slew of additional features and a streamlined, refreshed user interface to make your workspace a stress-free, usable oasis.